qld.gov.au 2017-06-26

# Privacy | Queensland Government

The Queensland Government manages personal information in line with the [_Information Privacy Act 2009_ (PDF, 836 KB)](http://www.legislation.qld.gov.au/LEGISLTN/CURRENT/I/InfoPrivA09.pdf).

We collect and manage your personal information as described on this page, unless stated otherwise. 'Personal information' may include your name, address, phone number, email address, age, gender, your employer, and your position title.

## Information we may request

We may ask you to provide personal information through this site. We will only do this:

  * to meet your needs (e.g. answer a question, provide a service)
  * to meet our needs (e.g. demographic analysis)
  * if required by law.

## Use and disclosure of personal information

We will not add you to a mailing list, or give your personal information to third parties without your consent, unless required by law.

## Emails

Our privacy principles apply to emails as well.

Our internet service provider or information technology staff may monitor email traffic for system trouble shooting and maintenance purposes only

## Cookies

We use cookies to collect anonymous statistical information, including:

  * your browser, computer platform and screen resolution
  * your traffic patterns through our site, such as: 
    * the date and time of your visit
    * the pages and documents accessed
    * the website you visited before ours
    * your server address.

We do not identify users or any browser activity outside this website, except in the unlikely event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may have a warrant to inspect activity logs.

Transactional services available from this site may use cookies to track business processes. Please read the particular service's privacy and security statement before beginning a transaction.

## Website analytics

We use Google Analytics (including display advertising features) on our website to gather anonymous information about visitors to our website. When you visit our web pages, your browser automatically sends anonymous information to Google. Examples of the information include the web address of the page that you're visiting, your IP address and demographic information. Google may also use cookies.

We use this data to analyse the pages that are visited, to improve your experience and make sure our website is useful.

You can read more about [how Google uses data](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You can choose not to allow Google to collect your information by [opting out of Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) or specifically opt out of [Google Analytics display advertiser features](http://www.google.com.au/policies/technologies/ads).

## Security

Parts of this site transmit information securely across the internet. However this is not always feasible. We recognise that there may be risks transmitting information across the internet. We will notify you where personal information is not transmitted securely.

Where this site contains links to other Queensland Government agencies’ websites, the privacy or security terms set out there will apply to the material on the websites.

Where this site contains links to non-Queensland Government websites, the Queensland Government is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of any such websites.

## More information

[Email us](mailto:Government.Gateway@qld.gov.au) if you would like to know more about information privacy.
